The crime of a lifetime. Live on the net.
Stealing Candy is a thriller film directed by Mark L. Lester.
Three ex-cons kidnap a famous movie star and force her to film a
sex tape live on the internet for a paying audience.
Candy Tyler, played by Jenya Lano.
Brad Vorman, played by Coolio.
Fred Dowd, played by Alex McArthur.
Walt Gearson, played by Daniel Baldwin.
Mr. Spinelli, played by Jeff Wincott.
Talk Show Host, played by Adrienne Meltzer.
Stealing Candy is a 2003 thriller film directed by Mark L.
Lester and starring Daniel Baldwin.
It was produced by Lester's production company American World Pictures.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, ex-con, movie star.
The tone is intense.